<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Smart Attendance</string>
    <string name="message">Smart attendance message</string>

    <string-array name="help_headings">
        <item>How the system works</item>
        <item>Adding Courses</item>
        <item>Taking Attendance</item>
        <item>Marking Attendance</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="help_infos">

        <!--how this actually works info-->
        <item>
            \n1. Both Teacher and Student adds the teaching or enrolled courses.
            \n2. Teacher will announce the Attendance mode to the students (WiFi or Bluetooth).
            \n3. Students will select the mode, enter the row, column of their seated bench.
            \n4. Teacher will get the attendance list either through Bluetooth or WiFi, which can be uploaded to Google Sheets by the teacher.
            \n5. Teacher can cross check the present students with the help of Virtual Map of the class, and proxies if any, can be removed.
            \n6. In case any student has not brought his phone, or somehow is not able to use the app, the Teacher can manually add his/her roll number.
        </item>

        <!--adding courses info-->
        <item>1. Add Courses one at a time by tapping Plus button in the dashboard.
        \n2. Enter the details of the course and the range of enrolled students of the course.
        \n3. Tap the tick button and select your Google Sheets account to store the Attendance sheet.
        \n4. Wait for the sheet to upload and that\'s it! You can see all the added courses in your dashboard.
        \n5. This step requires internet connection.
        </item>

        <!--taking attendance info:-->
        <item>1. Choose any course to take attendance from the dashboard.
        \n2. Choose WiFi or Bluetooth mode and tap on \'Take Attendance\'.
        \n3. Tap on \'Start Scanning\' and wait for a minute or two.
        \n4. Tap on \'Stop Scanning\' and check the Virtual Map to visualise the present students in the class.
        \n5. You can check for proxies by just cross checking the count of students in each bench.
        \n6. You can add/remove any roll number by tapping on the bench in the virtual map.
        \n7. Before saving the attendance, add the number of hours of the class and tap on \'Save Attendance\'.
        \n8. That\'s it! You can go back and upload the attendance to Google sheets anytime.
        </item>

        <!--marking attendance info-->
        <item>
            \n1. Select the Course and Attendance mode.
            \n2. Enter the row and column of the Bench.
            \n3. If the attendance mode is WiFi, you need to turn on the Hotspot manually.
            \n4. Hotspot name will be generated and will be copied directly to the clipboard once you tap on \'Mark Attendance\'.
            \n5. Paste the generated name and turn on the Hotspot and go back.
            \n6. If the attendance mode is Bluetooth, the process will be done automatically.
        </item>

    </string-array>


</resources>
